agrifarming.in 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy&Terms | Agrifarming.in

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our on-line information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Google Ad sense and the Double Click DART Cookie Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> .Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google ads own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies,[ www.agrifarming.in](http://agrifarming.in/) no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

Collection of Personal Information When visiting [www.agrifarming.in](http://agrifarming.in/) , the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyse trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Links to third party Websites We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

Changes to this Privacy Statement The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

Content provided on this website [www.agrifarming.in](http://agrifarming.in/) is only for information, we are not responsible for any loss that you may incur in [agriculture farming](http://www.agrifarming.in/agriculture-farming/). please consult any of agricultural technical officer or adviser before using the information.

All information provided in these articles is based either on personal experience or information provided by others In all cases, it is your responsibility to obtain veterinary services and advice before using any of the information provided in these articles or on this website . Neither [http://agrifarming.in](http://agrifarming.in/) nor any of the contributors to this website will be held responsible for the use of any information contained herein.
